[
    {
        "question": "Secure your Crypto!",
        "answer": "BEST PROJECT EVER"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forks Explained",
        "answer": "Go Get"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ton voices live",
        "answer": "I LOVE BLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "How to Analyze crypto?",
        "answer": "VALUE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Navigating Crypto",
        "answer": "HEYBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Telegram Mini Apps?",
        "answer": "CRYPTOBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Say No to Rug Pull!",
        "answer": "SUPERBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Are AMMs?",
        "answer": "CryptoSmart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liquidity Pools Guide",
        "answer": "BLUMERSSS"
    },
    {
        "question": "$2.5M+ DOGS Airdrop",
        "answer": "HAPPYDOGS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doxxing? What's that?",
        "answer": "NODOXXING"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pre-Market Trading?",
        "answer": "WOWBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Play track & type track name",
        "answer": "Blum - Big City Life"
    },
    {
        "question": "How To Memecoin?",
        "answer": "Memeblum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Token Burning: How & Why?",
        "answer": "Onfire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Terms. Part 1?",
        "answer": "Blumexplorer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bitcoin Rainbow Chart?",
        "answer": "soblum"
    },
    {
        "question": "How to trade Perps?",
        "answer": "CRYPTOFAN"
    },
    {
        "question": "How To Find Altcoins?",
        "answer": "ULTRABLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "DeFi Explained",
        "answer": "Blumforce"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sharding Explained",
        "answer": "Blumtastic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Slang. Part 1",
        "answer": "BLUMSTORM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pumptober Special",
        "answer": "PUMPIT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is On-chain Analysis?",
        "answer": "BLUMEXTRA"
    },
    {
        "question": "DeFi Risks: Key Insights",
        "answer": "BLUMHELPS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Choosing a Crypto Exchange",
        "answer": "CRYPTOZONE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Slang. Part 2",
        "answer": "FOMOOO"
    },
    {
        "question": "DeFi Risks: Key Insights",
        "answer": "BLUMHELPS"
    }
]
